Dear Hiring Team,

My name is Brandon Nadeau and I am writing to express my interest in the IT Administrator role at Decision Technology, INC. I was informed about your company by a friend who is currently in your employment, Dalton Ballance.

While I don't currently specialize in IT, I do have a broad education in everything computer related. I enjoy building complex computer systems that involve specialized hardware and facilitating devices to communicate and share resources over multiple networks. When I did focus more on IT I self educated myself in topics such CCNA based networking, setting up servers, building computers, and playing with an extensive number of operating systems such as windows based systems and unix based systems which include macOs, chromeOs, and a large variety of linux distributions ranging from ubuntu, fedora, debian, arch, centOS, redhat, and more.

Another topic I spent time educating myself on was cybersecurity, which involved practices such as reconnaissance and information gathering, vulnerability assessment, exploiting systems, and updating vulnerable systems. This education reached every level of complexity from high-level concepts and theories to using industry based services and tools to creating my own tools and touched on reverse engineering existing applications to discover unfound vulnerabilities.

For the last couple of years I focused on specializing in full stack engineering. This involves setting up databases controlled by a backend server which communicates securely to a frontend interface such as a website or mobile app. I prefer to focus on backend and frontend functionality or building reusable libraries over practicing UX/UI design. However, I have spent more time recently enchancing my design abilities to deliver a clean and friendly UX/UI experience. The only skill in this area that is considerably weak is production. Production involves primarily setting up hosting environments on AWS which is currently the industry standard for production. While I have used AWS to set up databases and host applications in the past, it is a skill that I am still a novice in and prefer to use alternative services such as Heroku and Google Domains for hosting as of now.

Recently I have started education in Artificial Intelligence using standardized courses available on Coursera that were developed by leading AI experts. I currently have a single certificate out of the four required to hold an authenticated specialization in the Deep Learning subfield of AI, which has garnered public attention in applications such as ChatGPT and Dalle from OpenAI.

I would say my greatest skill however is the ability to educate myself and the ability to problem solve.

Thank you for your time, I hope you consider me for a role in your company. I can't wait to be part of your team and help achieve company goals

Sincerely, Brandon Nadeau

# Brandon Nadeau

Charlotte, NC • email@bnadeau.dev • (704) 614-6831

Portfolio | Github | Stackoverflow | Linkedin

## **Personal Summary**

Programming since the age of 12, and tech enthusiast before that, I have a versatile skill set that includes multiple languages and frameworks. I have explored both low and high-level languages. I have experience in cybersecurity, networking (CCNA + socket programming), frontend and backend development, databases, mobile development, data gathering (web scraping), AI and more. I always strive to expand my skill set and explore cutting edge technology and services.

**Languages:** Python, JavaScript/TypeScript, C++, C#, Rust

Web Frameworks: ReactJs, Django, Flask, Dotnet

#### Education

**University of North Carolina Charlotte** 

BAS, Software Development

Charlotte, NC

Attended, 2021-2022

**Central Piedmont Community College** 

AAS, Computer Science

Charlotte, NC

Transfer, 2019-2021

### Experience

**Prismatic Logistics LLC Delivery Driver** 

Charlotte, NC

Dec 2022 - Present

- Demonstrated strong initiative in completing designated tasks independently.
- Collaborated with team members to optimize customer satisfaction by efficiently sharing and organizing work loads.
- Contributed to a positive and supportive team culture, consistently striving for the highest levels of productivity and customer service.

**OBI Seafoods LLC Quality Control** 

Naknek, AK

May 2019 - Aug 2022

- Maintained high levels of product quality through effective oversight of production processes.
- Streamlined company production records by digitizing and organizing them for efficient use.
- Implemented required technology on company fleet in compliance with Alaska state law, ensuring reliable delivery of safe seafood products.
- Adapted the HoboWare quality control hardware/software to facilitate consistent data collection protocols throughout the company's large merger.

SoCo Growers LLC

Rve, CO

Horticulturist

May 2017 - July 2018

- Implemented daily care and maintenance practices to optimize the health and growth of all flora.
- Developed effective pest management strategies to ensure optimal plant growth and prevent damage.
- Maintained excellent relationships with retail vendors through timely and efficient delivery of flora products.

### **Petro Marine Services**

Sitka, AK

Jan 2014 – Jun 2014

- Attendant • Responsible for the opening and closing of the marina.
  - Provided an array of services for fishing and other large vessels